"I Walk The Line" Johnny Cash
* I keep a close watch on this heart of mine *
* I keep my eyes wide open all the time *
* I keep the ends out for the tie that binds *
司机:Sergei Malatov
* Because you're mine *
* I walk the line *
银色宝马: Sergei的车
Petrovna Ilona 绿色捷豹S型
* I find it very very easy to be true *
* I find myself alone when each day is through *
* Yes, I'll admit I'm a fool for you *
* Because you're mine *
* I walk the line *
老大? 手机: 410-959 0875
* As sure as night is dark and day is light *
* I keep you on my mind both day and night *
* And happiness I've known proves that it's right *
车险: Eastpoint保险
* I walk the line *
Eton Ben-Eleazer: 银色沃尔沃S80
* You've got a way to keep me on your side *
* You give me cause for love that I can't hide *
Baltimore  毒品
毒贩
* For you I know I'd even try to turn the tide *
* Because you're mine *
* I walk the line *
George Glekas:黑色奥迪A4
* I keep a close watch on this heart of mine *
* I keep my eyes wide open all the time *
偷窃&销赃 绰号"双G" George Glekas
* I keep the ends out for the tie that binds *
* Because you're mine I walk the line *
帅呆了
Fucking a.
火线重案组 第二季 第十集 风雨欲来
The Wire S02E10 Storm Warnings
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"雇佣工会会员干活就是好"  ---Ziggy
嗯 货不错 给
Yeah, shit is good. Here.
听着 下回再补货的时候 告诉Moe我们需要
Next time we re-up, though... tell Moe man we need
再加个七八百包 懂吗
about 700, 800 more of them dimes, all right?
我操 我从没见过这么好卖的货
I ain't even seen shit like this since I don't know when.
Jumbo也是?(混合了高纯度可卡因的大麻)
Same with the jumbos?
嗯 最好都多带点
Yeah, better get more of those, too.
我操又有什么事? String 你好 伙计
What the fuck is up now? String, what's up, man?
你好 电话没法说
What up? Can't call it.
我们的货怎么样
How's our package?
你自己看 货很好
How's it look? Shit is good.
看见从东区来的家伙没?
See these Eastside motherfuckers over here?
我要你好好招待那些家伙...
I want you to extend to these motherfuckers...
我们西区可是有热情好客的美名 听见了吗?
all the hospitality that West Baltimore is famous for. You heard?
- 你想让我们把他们赶走? - 不 小伙
- Yeah, you want us to fuck them up? - No, dawg.
给他们221栋734栋 还有Saratoga街的那栋
We're giving them 221, 734, and Saratoga.
剩下的我们留下 要是有任何人找茬...
We keep the rest. If anybody start any shit...
他们就直接来找我 懂吗? 直接找我
they'll have to answer to me, all right? Directly.
你听到了吧?
You heard me, right?
好的
All right.
这些外人来公房区干嘛?
What are these off-brand niggers gonna do with a project tower?
一边呆着去 小伙
Fall back, young 'un.
我们要给你们这群鸟人看看 我们是怎么在这儿打拼的
We're gonna show y'all motherfuckers how to grind out here, all right?
嗨 String
Hey, String.
我听见你说的了 伙计 我听见了
I heard you, man, I did.
但是这事儿没道理啊
But this shit right here, it don't make no sense.
你喜欢我们的新品 对吧?
You like the new product we selling?
有道理了吧
It make sense now?
对于老大 我们调查的如何了?
Where are we at with our Boss Man?
我们应该很快就能监听他的电话了
We should be up on his phone soon.
涉案依据摆在那儿呢 毋庸置疑
The PC is there, no question.
一旦监听了他的手机 他就完了
We get up on his cell phone, he's done.
- 我们就能查清他的身份 没问题的 - 我说不好
-  We'll ID him, no problem. - I don't know.
我们当初刺探的时候 他们就停用了仓库电话
They came down on that warehouse phone when we spooked them.
Sobotka的手机也是 也许会是个死胡同
Sobotka's cell phone, too. We might be going up on a dead line.
还有一个办法
This is the other way to go.
和监听相比 这方法得放"长线"
Compared to the wiretap, it's the longer way around.
不过 要是他真换了手机...
But still, if he's changing up on his cell phone...
大概在上周
Over the last week or so...
我们不仅确认了几名主要嫌疑犯的身份...
we've not only confirmed the identities of some of the key players...
还在他们的车上装了GPS追踪器
we've also got GPS trackers on all their cars.
首先是...
First of all...
Eton Ben-Eleazer 他在货仓负责毒品
Eton Ben-Eleazer. He's the drug Lieutenant in the warehouse.
- 是E-ton - 随便
- E-ton. - Whatever.
我们的女士 Ilona Petrovna小姐
Our madam, Miss llona Petrovna.
George Glekas 他在高地区有家电器维修店
George Glekas, who runs the appliance store over in Highlandtown...
也是这个组织的外围门面
and the probable fence for the organization.
我们实时跟踪他们中的一些人
We followed some of them in real time.
通过这些小装置 我们可以另有作为
With this little toy here, there's something else we can do.
这是7天之内 我们的目标去过的地方的速览
That's seven days of where our targets have been, sped up.
看这儿 只有这两个地方... 有3 4两车同时停下
And lookit. Two locations only where three or four cars stopped
一起逗留了超过5分钟
at the same time for more than five minutes.
这个X标记的是一家位于南Clinton的路边小吃店
One "X" is a dive of a diner down on South Clinton.
另一处是在Edgemere南边 Howard堡的西岸
The other is on the western shore of Fort Howard down past Edgemere.
我们监视这些地方
We get up on these locations,
也许可以拍到一张老大的照片 或者车牌
maybe we get a photo of the Boss Man. Or a tag number.
棒极了 你从哪搞到这些东西的
It's totally cool. Where did you even get this stuff?
药管局提供的追踪器
DEA for the trackers.
McNulty从FBI当地办事处的伙计那儿 搞来了追踪软件
McNulty pulled the software from his pals at the FBI field office.
我们可以让Herc和Carver 从货仓撤出来去监视小吃店
We can pull Herc and Carver off the warehouse and give them the diner.
McNulty Bunk 你们负责Howard堡
McNulty, Bunk, you guys take Fort Howard.
搞什么 Frank
What the fuck, Frank?
你不妨就直接贴出来吧
You might as well start posting them things, right?
我是说 该死的 如果你要竞选 你不妨站出来直说
I mean, shit, if you're gonna run, you might as well come out and say so.
这不是为我自己考虑 Ott
It ain't personal, Ott.
我只是想把我提出的疏浚工程做完
I want to finish what I started with the dredging issue.
而你觉得我没本事搞定
And you don't think I'm good enough to handle it.
不是这个意思 小子
It ain't about that, kiddo.
Ott 听我说
Ott, listen to me!
你他妈要我怎么做? 告诉他钱是从哪儿来的?
What the fuck do you want me to do? Tell him where the money comes from?
码头工会?
I.B.S?
不是自夸 我们FBI调查团伙诈骗案是得心应手
Not to brag, but union racketeering is one thing the Bureau does well.
这就是我想听到的
That is exactly what I wanted to hear.
这个案子要尽快了结 伙计们
This case needs closure, boys.
并且我由衷地认为...
And in my heart of hearts...
你们是能把Sobotka绳之以法的人
I know you're the kind of bastards to put Sobotka where he needs to be.
还有一件你们FBI可以帮我的事
One other thing you Federals can help me with.
如果可以的话
And if you don't mind,
请尽量谨慎处理
a little discretion is called for.
这上面的是我区一辆刑侦车...
That, right there, is the district surveillance van...
丢的时候还是满载着装备
which was fully equipped when it disappeared.
- 一辆刑侦车? - Sobotka偷了它
- A surveillance van? - Sobotka stole it.
现在它不知所踪
Now it's l-don't-know-where.
最后一张照片是在西雅图...
The last picture was from Seattle...
但是我从另外两个地方的...
but I got prints...
照片上发现了指纹 瞧
from two other places, see?
你上报了这件盗车案 对吧?
You reported the van stolen, right?
我觉得
It was my feeling
一起发生在警局停车场的偷车案...
that the theft of a vehicle from a departmental lot...
会使警局蒙羞
would reflect poorly on the department.
其实 我知道你们有办法...
The thing is, I know you boys have got enough reach...
把车弄回来而不引起骚动
to maybe get the van back without no big dustup.
作为我给你们整个案子的回报
As a favor for me having brought you the whole case.
狗日的东区王八蛋 应该滚回自己的地盘去
Motherfucking Eastside need to get their asses back across town where they belong.
哟 伙计 把他们赶走 就是把好货赶走...
Yo, man, we run them off, we run off the good dope so...
我只是说
I'm just saying
他们总是到处压价抢生意
they all the time hustling around cutting prices and doing shit.
这不对
It ain't right.
跟我来 伙计
Walk, nigger.
哟 怎么了 士兵
Yo, what's up, soldier?
看看能不能搞点货
Looking maybe to do something here.
和他 这王八蛋?
With him? This motherfucker?
我上周在Ashland看见他卖假货
I saw him over on Ashland last week selling burns.
- 操你大爷 死鬼 - 瞧 他开价多少?
- Fuck y'all, nigger. - Look, what did he say?
25块 两包货外加一支可卡因
$25, two dimes and a coke kicker.
我15块卖你两包 外加免费顶级冰毒 咋样?
I'll give you two dimes for $15, plus the ice on top for free. What?
成交
That'll work.
先到门廊那儿 我就在你后面
Take it in the lobby. I'll be right behind you.
这才对 看见了没? 现在
That's what's up, see? The game now
我们要努力比他们卖得多
is that we gotta sell more of this good shit than they do.
什么 给我滚远
What? Get the fuck out of here!
你是想告诉我 西区能有黑鬼...
You mean to tell me there's a Westside nigger...
可以不动刀不动枪 不搞强买强卖?
who knows how to sell shit without sticking a pistol in a fiend's face?
是啊 伙计
Yeah, dawg.
你们最好趁早习惯 因为你们以后一包也卖不出去了!
And you better get used to it. 'cause y'all ain't selling shit
除非我们卖到断货 相信我!
until we bone-ass dry. Believe that.
好吧 小子 随便你 伙计
All right, nigger. Whatever, man.
好的 软蛋大奶的贱B
All right, cottage-cheese, chest-ass motherfucker.
这东西放哪儿
Where do you want it?
那边就行
There's good.
小心点
Easy.
我们可以帮你装好
We could help you set it up.
你们不用去监视吗?
You have a surveillance to cover?
- 我又有那种感觉了 - 当我们没学过怎么坐马桶似的(给小孩和宠物的训练)
- I got that feeling again. - Like they don't think we're potty trained.
有事吗
Can I help you?
我们是FBI Daniels警督在吗
FBI. Lt. Daniels?
在他办公室
He's in his office.
要是没那证件在我脸前晃 我还真瞧不出来
Without that billboard in my face, I wouldn't have known.
怎么看得出来啊
How could you have known?
尖头皮鞋
There was the wingtips.
一双眯眯眼 绝对露馅
And the beady eyes. Definite giveaway.
- 还有结实的屁股 - 绝对暴露了
- Tight asses. - Definitely.
Daniels队长 特工Settles和Mason
Lt. Daniels? Agents Settles and Mason.
Valchek警长说你在等我们
Maj. Valchek said you'd be expecting us.
你听听这白痴说的
You listening to this fool?
说东区比西区要野蛮...
Saying that the Eastside is wilder than Westside...
因为东区的爱喝波特酒(带甜味的非烈性酒)
'cause of some shit about Eastside folks drinking port wine...
而西区的爱喝雪利酒(烈性酒)
while the Westside do sherry?
波特酒也能让人发酒疯
Port make a man do crazy shit,
我告诉你
I'm telling you.
Butchie 说说这白痴
Butchie, talk to this fool.
就我看来 东西两地说的上的区别...
For me, leastways the difference between East and Weste
得追溯到一个人身上 Frank Mattews
goes back to one man: Frank Matthews.
Pee Wee ("小人物")Matthews(美国大毒枭)
Pee Wee Matthews?
是的 这家伙北上纽约 和意大利人做生意
Yeah, the brother went up New York and got in bed with them Italians.
一桩美国真实的贩毒走私案
是这里唯一在"法国贩毒网"里分了一杯羹的人
The only one from this town got a piece of that French Connection.
Pee Wee跟这有啥关系?
What the hell Pee Wee got to do with anything?
因为Frank是西区人
'Cause Frank was Westside.
你觉得呢 毒从西区来
How do you like that? The dope flowed West.
当有了稳定货源 生意自然来
When you got a steady supply, you run shit like a business.
有人失意是理所当然
Somebody gets hurt, there's a reason.
不像如今这般愚蠢
Not like this foolishness we got today.
抱歉
Excuse me.
什么事 Omar
What say, Omar?
没啥事
Ain't no thing.
你知道吗 我有点东西要给你
You know I got something for you, right?
我不会空着手来
Wouldn't come around unless I did.
咋样Butch 最近如何 宝贝
What up, Butch? How you holding up, baby?
除了为你担忧 都挺好
Except for fretting on you, I'm good.
这给我的人
It's for my people.
以备不时之需
A little something for a rainy day.
这几年你也有点积蓄了
You built up a right nice-size nest these past couple of years.
也许什么时候你愿意回来
Might be time you maybe think about backing off some?
回来干啥
Back off to what?
再会 Butch
Later, Butch.
别动 宝贝
Stay, boy.
操 Zig 我还没剪开呢
Damn, Zig, I ain't got it cut yet.
把收音机关掉 看在上帝的份上!
And turn that shit down, for Christ's sake.
干得好
Nicely done.
就像我一直说的 雇佣工会会员干活就是好
Like I always say, it pays to go with a union card every time.
把收音机关了 Zig
Turn the fucking radio down, Zig.
你现在他妈的可以上车了吗?
Will you get in the goddamn car already?
上帝啊 我们不能整晚呆在这
For Christ's sake, we ain't got all night.
上帝
Jesus!
从这个洞开辆坦克过去也刮不到
You could drive a tank through there, it wouldn't take a scratch.
这是打算运到哪儿去?
Where the fuck you going with this?
希腊 雅典 希腊
Greece. Athens, Greece.
剪了这个洞 他们就不会怀疑是内鬼了
The hole is so they don't think it's an inside job.
他们就不会去查工会
So they don't look at the union.
"欢迎登船 头儿"
Welcome aboard, chief.
是你吗
Is that you?
我以为你去买东西了
I thought you were gonna go shopping.
- 我? - 是的
- Me? - Yeah.
我们可是监视了一整天
We round-the-clock with surveillance.
那什么时候你能说 "我都是在为你干这干那"?
When do we get to the part where you do all kind of shit for me?
什么时候啊?
When do we get to that part?
怎么 你就不提 谁给你拿的那几个购物袋了?
So you past the point of lifting a grocery bag or two?
那你试试像我这样
You try being me like this.
有心事?
Something wrong?
宝宝在踢我
The baby's kicking.
想感觉一下吗?
Wanna feel?
- 要将近四千! - 我知道
- Almost $4,000. - I know it is.
那个开仓库的希腊人 付我现金
The Greek guy, the one with the warehouse, pays me in cash.
为了不用记账 就省得缴税费和福利了
Keeps it off the books, so he don't have to pay taxes and benefits.
而你一分都没花?
And you saved all that?
他还给我升了职 我现在一周能挣七百
He gave me a bump, too. I'm pulling down $700 a week.
你不信我?
You don't believe me?
上帝
Christ.
我这么存钱是为了给你找个新公寓
I was saving that up to give to you for the new apartment.
你知道我的意思 伙计
You know what I'm saying, dawg?
但是我不明白 这些个婊子怎么就这样呢
But I don't understand how these hoes be acting sometimes and shit.
如果我开口 我就会说“贱人 你要么给哥好好舔 要么就滚蛋”
If I tell a bitch, I'm like, "Bitch, either you suck dick or you don't."
先生们
Gentlemen.
咋的 伙计?
What's up, my brother?
你是往这推销豆饼吗 你明白我的意思吗
Are you slinging bean pies up in here? You know what I mean?
全美伊斯兰联盟会 黑人运动团体 曾以推销豆饼筹资
你是那个联盟的吗?
You with the nation, homey?
西装蝴蝶结是联盟成员的标志
因为你要么是个穆斯林...
'Cause either you're a Muslim...
要么就别让你老妈  每天早上给你放上学要穿的衣服了
or your momma need to stop laying your clothes out in the morning.
我是代表Barksdale先生来到此地
I'm here to represent the interests of a Mr. Barksdale.
你们熟悉Barksdale先生吗?
Are you familiar with Mr. Barksdale?
听说过 我也不是无名之辈
That name ring out, but so do mine.
你是谁?
And you are?
"Cheese" 伙计
Cheese, man.
Cheese先生 我知道了
Mr. Cheese. I see.
你为谁工作 Cheese先生?
And who do you work for, Mr. Cheese?
我为谁工作?
Who do I work for?
你不是Barksdale先生的雇员 对吗?
Am I correct in assuming that you are not employed by Mr. Barksdale?
嗯 是啊
Hell, yeah.
如果是这样的话 那我就得让你离开
If that is the case, then I have to insist that you leave.
- 这黑鬼是认真的? - 让我强调一下
- This nigger serious? - Let me be emphatic.
你得跟滚到Charles街另一边 那才是你该呆的地方
You need to take your black ass across Charles Street to where it belong.
- 啥? - 等下
- What? - Hold on now.
他还搞不清状况 这不是他想的那样 你明白吗
He don't know what this is. It ain't what he think, you know what I'm saying?
首先
First of all,
我们得到允许 在高楼区这边做生意
we got permission to grind in these here towers.
其次 我他妈的...
Second of all, I don't give a fuck...
放开我 放开
Get off me, get off!
这是塑胶丸 小铅弹
Pellets in plastic. Rat shot.
你需要在意的是 现在枪膛里的这一发是什么
What you need to be concerned about is what's seated in the chamber now:
一个铜皮空心弹...
A copper-jacketed, hollow point...
重120格令 新鲜出炉自制小弹丸(格令:英美制最小重量单位)
120-grain hot street load of my own creation.
所以你应该好好思考一下
So you need to think for just a moment
并且问自己
and ask yourself:
我应该做些什么
What do I have to do
才不会让这个男人再对我开枪
before this man raise up his gun again?
走吧
Let's go.
一路走好 先生
Good day to you, sir.
我很同意特工们的评估
I'm in agreement with the agents' assessment.
就我看来这个案子很适合用《联邦反诈骗操纵贿赂法案》(反黑法)进行起诉
As far as I can see. this case is an ideal candidate for RICO prosecution.
我处也同意依据该法案起诉
My agency agrees RICO is the way to go,
那么将在你们联邦法院进行审理 而不是我们地方法院
so we'll be in your courthouse, not mine.
但是我要强调一点
But I want one thing on record.
因为911事件 联邦调查局对此案有优先权
As of 9l11, the Bureau has one priority in this case:
必须以码头腐败立案
It's waterfront corruption.
现在世道不同了 而码头是薄弱环节
It's a new world and the ports are vulnerable.
这个案子不仅仅牵扯到工会
This case is bigger than the union.
我们同意的是接管整个案件 队长
We're agreeing to take on the whole case, Lieutenant.
而正是因为"工会"问题 才让我们坐到了一起
But the union is why we're in the room with you.
如果你们同意 我们就可以并肩作战了
If you're okay with that, we can work the case together.
届时我们将会复制所有调查报告 给到警督和Pearlman女士
We'll copy all the Bureau's 302s to the Lieutenant and Miss Pearlman.
同样 你们的资料副本也必须 送到第6小队和我的办公室
Your paperwork should CC Squad 6 and my office, as well.
好的
okay.
我要开始把你们的案卷 录入我们的系统里
I'll start pumping your casework into our system.
看看会有什么发现
See what leads that might generate.
你不躺下歇着?
Oughtn't you be laid up resting?
枪伤可不是小事情
A gunshot ain't nothing to trifle with.
肩膀是挺疼
Shoulder do hurt.
但是这里 功能正常
But this here work just fine.
告诉Stack把它擦干净 贴上售价$7.50
Tell Stack to polish it up good and put $7.50 on it.
多好的烤面包机 电线磨损了就扔掉 太可惜了
Shame to let a good toaster get away over a frayed cord.
首先 没人在公房区占上风
First off, ain't nobody running up in them projects.
那些西区的家伙没了货源 会比你更受伤
Them Westside boys are hurting over this more than even you.
相信我 只要我们给的好货卖光了 他们就玩完了
Trust me, soon as our good shit run out, they fucked.
其次
Second,
暗杀过Mouzone大兄的杀手海了去了
a whole passel of hard-ass hitters took a go at Brother Mouzone,
没一个能活下来炫耀的
and ain't lived to say shit about it.
要是我们去对付那家伙 不知道会捅出什么乱子
We go at the boy, no telling what might get stirred up.
如果Stringer出手
If Stringer takes a shot,
那他就是跟Avon过不去
he crosses Avon on it.
那就出钱买他人头
Put a bounty on him.
找几个毒鬼在他背后开黑枪
Let some bushwacking fiend back-shoot his ass.
我出钱找人干他 让他发现之后第一个就来找我?
I pin money on him, and first thing he come at me?
操
Shit.
还不如现在就给自己一枪 一了百了
Might as well just shoot myself now and get it over.
有一个家伙兴许能干成这事
There is one boy who might could just pull this off.
也只有他不会收佣金
Only, he won't take contract money.
瞄准人群中心 一枪一个不要失手
Aim for center mass. Make sure the man goes down.
没问题
No problem.
左边3个是我的
I got the three on the left.
草你大爷 混蛋
Fuck you, assholes.
- 你好 - 你好 伙计
- How you doing? - How you doing, buddy?
三星S221 有吗?
The Samsung S221. You got that?
没有啊
I don't see it.
在清点库房 是吗
Doing the old inventory, are we?
我希望没有人监守自盗噢
I hope there ain't been no thieving going on.
不要像我们码头那样总是丢东西
Not like the problem we got down at the docks.
你把车运走了?
You get the cars off?
已经在里海航行了2小时了
Sailed two hours ago on the Caspia.
登记的是废铝
Listed as scrap aluminum.
- 我拿到了提单 - 不要在这
- I got the bill of lading right here. - Not here.
去我办公室
In my office.
请原谅 但是我怎么才能知道...
Forgive me, but how am I to know.
你没有运个空箱子过去
you did not ship them empty?
我不知道 我看一下
I just don't know. Let me see.
也许我要是有个400万像素
Maybe if I had a 4.0 Megapix,
3倍变焦 全数字照相机...
three time optical, fully digitalized camera...
我就能给装进集装箱里的奔驰汽车 拍几张高清照片了
I could've taken some quality photos of them Benzes in those cans.
但是 噢 我忘了 我的照相机被摔坏了
But oops. I forgot my camera got busted.
或者你瞧 我还能怎么办
Or you know what I could do?
我可以让Boris躲进码头...
I could get old Boris to skulk around them docks...
用满是血丝的老眼盯着那些集装箱
keep the old commie red eye on them containers.
确保那些码头工人 不会把手脚动到我头上
Make sure the dock boys are playing me straight.
- 是按我的要求吗 - 是的
- They are what I order? - Yes.
S系列 我是按照你要求的颜色找的
I got you the S series in the colors that you wanted.
我还停了一辆在外面 你想看看吗
I even got one parked outside. You wanna see?
外面? 现在?
Outside? Now?
我就是带她兜兜风 长官
I'm just taking her out for a spin, chief.
今晚一定把她送回去
I'll put her back tonight.
等一下
Wait one.
每辆车起码值6万
Them cars list out at better than $60,000 each.
两成是上周谈的 今天我报价一成
20% was last week.Today, the quote is 10%.
不论如何
Still,
几小时就挣这么多 很不错了
it's good money for a few hours' work.
不
No!
他妈的不可能
No fucking way!
我们有协议 混蛋 有协议!
We had a deal, motherfucker. A deal.
你听我说 是我他妈的在外面冲锋陷阵 我
You listen to me. It was my fucking ass out there on the line. Mine.
这点屁钱 你是打发叫花子啊
This piddling shit is the best that you come up with?
你他妈别想玩我 别想
You don't play me like that. You don't.
操你妈
Fuck you,
你个不要脸的希腊贱货
you thieving, Greek cunt.
傻逼
Malaka!
这句你不知道 "头儿" 但是你懂"Malaka" 是吧?
You don't know that one, chief. But you know "malaka," yes?
你现在也知道什么是"穿着衣服的傻逼"了
Now you know malaka with dress.
不要
Please.
傻逼
Malaka.
能听见我说话吗
Can you hear me?
如果你能说话的话 请不要挂电话
If you can talk, please stay on the line.
先上船 再穿救生衣
Get in the boat first, then put the preserver on.
- 那样会舒服点 - 真的?
- It's easier that way. - Yeah?
你们他妈的就是想淹死我
Y'all trying to drown my ass for sure.
上来
Come on.
别推啊 伙计
Don't push me, man.
鱼竿
Rod.
拿到了
Got it.
这儿 抓住
Here. Hold on to that.
我会用 我会用这个
I know this one.
Stringer Bell为了这事来找我
Stringer Bell will come at me with this.
说他和Omar之间有些事情要了结
Says he's got something with Omar he need to make straight.
没说是什么事?
Didn't say what that might be?
不会跟我说的
Wouldn't tell me.
但是说实话 我也不想知道
And to be truthful, I didn't want to know.
不
No.
我感觉不对劲
It don't feel right.
你知道Barksdale的那些家伙不值得信任
You know them Barksdale people ain't to be trusted.
你说的没错
No denying all you say is true.
但是Stringer说要谈判
But Stringer talking parley.
你的小伙计就应该好好考虑一下
So your boy needs to think long and hard on this.
因为只要Omar还想在街上混下去...
'Cause if Omar is living his day-to-day in the street...
不坐下来谈是不行的 谁也不知道他们下一步是什么
there ain't no telling what their next step might be if there ain't no sit-down.
"谈判"?
"Parley"?
他说这就是他要的
That's all he says he's looking for.
我会和他说的
I'll talk to him.
但是要是他跟我一样 认为这事很可笑...
But if it feels funny to him the way it does to me...
我可能受到无辜牵连 你懂吗?
I got a better chance of putting a leash to the wind, you know?
你要是觉得有帮助
If you think it might help,
我可以提供保护
I can go protection.
上次是他们吃了亏
They're the one got hurt the last time.
上次见面是有原因的
Then there was a reason to meet.
这次我觉得不一样
This time feel different.
你说的我懂
I hear you.
也许Stringer还是想了结恩怨
Maybe Stringer's still trying to settle that beef
毕竟他也得在这儿混下去...
behind the fact that he got to live in this city, too...
Omar就是Omar
Omar being Omar.
如果这是你的举手之劳
If it ain't putting you out none...
那保护一下我的侄子 会让我安心很多
I'd feel a powerful lot better if my nephew took over protection.
Hayward
Hayward.
J.H. "独立宣言"上最醒目的一个签名 后人用它来指亲笔签名
打好了 就差您的"亲笔签名"了
Typed and ready for your John Hancock.
- 多谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - Sure.
你在每页草签一下 最后一页签全名
You just have to initial each page and then sign at the end.
我就是看一看 这是官方文件 是吗 长官?
I'm just checking. This is the official record, right, chief?
这就是要提交给法庭的
It's what's gonna play in court.
我能改一下吗
Can I change something?
可以
Yeah.
只要...
Just
在你更改的地方旁边签个名就可以了
put your initials next to your changes. It's no problem.
嗯 就一处
Yeah, it's only one.
你知道吗 你打的是“说”
You know, you typed "said"
这里
here, see?
"说"
"Said"?
嗯
Yeah
他没有
He wasn't
没有对我说"别对我开枪"
He wasn't saying, "Please don't shoot me."
更像是在求我
It was more begging.
你瞧
You know?
"双G"(绰号) 他是在求我
Double G, he's begging me.
这不会给你添乱吧 是吧
But that's not gonna mess you up, though, right?
不 只是更有描述性
No, it's more descriptive like that.
很好 多谢
It's good. Thanks.
没动静 没人进出这里
Quiet. No one in or out of there.
这里真不错
It's kind of nice out here.
月光照在水面
Moonlight on the water.
浪花轻轻拍打船舷
Waves lapping gently against the boat.
朝九晚五的工作我能胜任 懂吗
I'm working my regular eight. I can handle it, you know?
但是像这种专案组...
But a detail like this...
这就是我要问你的
That's what I'm asking.
如果工作上有了麻烦
If something comes up on the job,
你怎么处理?
how would you handle it?
我的意思是 在家怎么面对孩子们
I mean, at home with the kids.
直到现在 还没有什么麻烦
Until now, not much came up.
比如说 有了什么麻烦
But now, say something comes up.
我的意思是 我们要进行一次突袭或别的什么
I mean, say we do a raid or something.
你会怎么做?
What would you do?
我猜我会叫保姆留下陪孩子过夜
I guess I'd try to get the sitter to stay.
找朋友帮个忙 就像今晚一样
Maybe call my folks, like I did tonight.
你知道带孩子怎么回事 他们身边离不开人
You know how it is with kids. You gotta be there.
但是你不就会错过吗
But you wouldn't miss it?
我的意思是 大家都出动了
I mean, with everybody rolling out
你却得直接回家?
and you having to head home?
如果一直如此 我也不知道该怎么做
If it keeps going like this, I don't know what I'm gonna do.
- 多谢 - 别客气
- Thanks. - It's no problem.
你想给什么人打个电话吗?
You wanna make a phone call to someone?
如果被转到Madison郡看守所 那就有段时间不能打电话了
If you get over to Madison, it might be some time before you can.
我没机会被保释吧?
Ain't a chance I get a bail, right?
家里人呢?
How about family?
好的 告诉你最新的情况
All right, to bring you up to speed,
我们让驻Le Havre(法国港口)的特工...
we've got agents in Le Havre...
从Talco公司近期将到这里的 船运清单里找线索
shagging leads from the manifest of the Talco ship due here in a few days.
看看能否查出有问题的集装箱的源头
To see if we can't pinpoint the origin for the illegal containers.
那可是不少的集装箱啊
That's a lot of cans.
准确的说是110个
A hundred and ten, actually.
你需要多少特工追查集装箱的来源?
How many agents you need to track back to where all those cans came from?
要多少有多少
As many as it takes.
我们也许很混蛋
We may be assholes,
但是在外面 我们这样的一抓一大把
but on the upside, there's an awful lot of us.
我来把这些输进电脑 传给海外那帮家伙
Let me get this into the computer for the boys overseas.
小吃店那边有什么消息吗?
Anything from that shithole of a diner?
Herc和Carver整夜都没发现什么
Herc and Carver had nothing overnight.
联邦调查局的监视了一早上 也没发现什么
The feds took over this morning and it's still quiet.
我回水上去
I'm going back on the water.
只要接头一次 我们就可以盯上这家伙
One meet and we're on this guy.
驻地:Baltimore 主管特工: Reese,Amanda 第六队 侦办特工:Mason,Settles
警告---机密信息监控 关键字:George Glekas; Serge Malatov
关键字:Ilona Peirovna Eton Ben-eleazer
电话监控:Pyramid公司 Serge Malatov
Talco船运周三到
The Talco line's in Wednesday.
我让Nick去取号码
I'll send Nick for a number.
- 又是希腊人? - 还有谁
- The Greeks again? - Who else?
就他们成天搞事 希腊人就这本事
They sure do stir up the shit, them Greeks do.
- Frank叔叔 - Nicky小侄 来的正好
- Uncle Frank. - Nicky boy, just in time.
- Frank叔叔 - 怎么了 发生什么事
- Uncle Frank. - What? What happened?
- 是Ziggy - 这次又捅了什么娄子?
- Ziggy. - What the fuck is it this time?
他开枪打了...
He shot...
他们说他开枪打了两个希腊人
They're saying he shot two of the Greeks.
- 昨晚 他们说的 - 开枪?
- Last night, they're saying. - Shot?
- 他开枪? - 老天爷!
- He shot? - Fucking Christ!
他被关起来了
He's locked up.
被指控谋杀罪!
He's fucking charged with murder.
- 希腊人? - 是"双G"
- The Greeks? - Double G.
还有一个在那条街上 给他店里干活的小孩
And one of the kids that works down the store on the avenue with him.
他们说他走进店里
They're saying he walked in there.
- 他走进店里 - 他去那干嘛?
- He went in. - Why was he there?
- 你在哪儿? 你他妈的在哪? - Frank叔叔 我不知道
- Where the fuck were you? - Uncle Frank, I didn't know.
你不知道什么?
What didn't you know?
- Ziggy去希腊人那里干什么 - 我不知道
- What is Ziggy doing near the Greeks? - I don't know.
你不知道 你应该知道 你他妈的是他堂兄!
You don't know? You're supposed to. You're his fucking cousin!
你是他父亲
You're his father.
1125 公斤
1,125 kilograms.
我对收缴毒品没有什么兴趣...
Not that drug enforcement's my cup of tea...
但是他们告诉我这是史上 最大的一次毒品收缴行动
but I'm told it was the largest crack seizure on record.
所以我希望我也能给你好消息
I just wish I had good news for you.
你告诉这是当地警方的行动
You told me this was a local effort.
现在事情搞大了 联邦调查局卷进来了
It's sprawled. Now the Bureau's involved.
我们一直监视着码头工会
We're looking hard at the port unions.
我也束手无策
My hands are tied.
他们在监听你们的电话
They're on you with wiretaps.
几个电话 几个地址
Several phones, several addresses.
让小伙子去找Eton
Have the boy go to Eton.
告诉他立即去另一头
Tell him to come right away to the other place.
- 你不直接打个电话? - 不用电话 不能再用电话
- You're not calling? - No phones. No more phones.
出什么事了
(speaking greek)
再见 我的朋友
Adieu, my friend.
他们忘了你的薯条
They forgot your fries.
不 是忘了"你的"
No, they forgot your fries.
我的薯条就在这儿
My fries are right in here.
那些是我的
Those are my fries.
贱人 我说什么你都回嘴
Bitch, everything I say, you hear backwards.
这是我的薯条 伙计
The fries are mine, boy.
吃吧
Go ahead.
吃你的薯条 死胖子 看我会不会鸟你
Eat the fries, you fat fuck. See if I fucking care.
啥?
What?
你认为我胖?
You think I'm fat?
就是这小伙
There's our boy.
Lester...Eton出来了
Lester, Eton's on the move.
收到
We got it.
需要人盯人吗?
No need for an eyeball follow, right?
不需要
No need.
好大一桶鱼啊
A fine fucking kettle of fish.
我听说了 但我要亲眼见一下
I heard it, but I had to come see it for myself.
- 这下我信了... - 警长?
- And sure enough... - Major?
知道吗 我对你们这群FBI寄予厚望
You know, I put my faith in you fucking feds.
你们却让我失望了
You let me down.
警长 我们可以去我办公室谈
Major, we can talk in my office.
警督
Lieutenant.
警督而已 对吧?
It's Lieutenant, right?
我给你的任务很简单
I gave you a simple assignment:
抓住那家伙 贴在角落那的家伙
That fellow, the one in the corner.
为了助你一臂之力 我帮你打点了这一切
And to make it happen, I gave you all this.
办案场所 人员...
Good digs, people...
所有你要的一切
everything you needed.
你回报了我什么?
And what did you give me?
背后踹了我一脚 队长!
Right up the fucking ass, Lieutenant.
- 警长 你会得到... - Roland 收拾你的东西
- Major, you're going to get... - Roland, get your shit.
你要按你的方法查 可以
You want to do it your way, fine.
但是你不能用我的人愚弄我
But you ain't gonna use my people to fuck me.
收拾东西 快点
Get your gear. I'm pulling you.
我...
I got...
还有事...你说...
There's work... You said...
快给我滚回警局...
Get your narrow ass back to the district...
否则以下犯上 我要打你屁屁了
before I slap you with insubordination.
快点 傻蛋!
Move, shitbird!
上帝!
Jesus!
警官 到我办公室
Detective, my office.
基地呼叫11-34
Base to 11-34.
两个目标正向你们移动
Target number two is coming at your 20.
收到 我们正在监视
Copy that. We're on it good.
我们看到老大了
We're on the Boss.
上帝
My God.
他打了两个?
He shoots both?
他杀了George 就在店里
He kills George, right there in the store.
留下了那孩子
Leaves the boy to bleed.
为什么?
For what?
就为那些车吵了起来?
An argument over a few cars?
- 那个小波兰佬 - 他疯了 那家伙
- That little Polack? - He's crazy, that one.
现在警察把他关起来了
The police have him now.
警察还在那儿?
The police still there?
去店里
Go to the store.
无论警察留下了什么
Whatever the police did not take,
文件 照片 任何东西... 你都要收拾干净
papers, pictures, everything... you clean it up.
仓库也是 所有的都要收拾干净
The warehouse, too. Everything gets clean now.
所有的
Everything.
不要再用电话
And the phones are dead.
你看到了吗? 他们刚刚把电话扔了
- Did you see that? - They just threw the phones.
11-34呼叫监视组
11-34 to Surveillance.
- 收到 - 我们确定目标了
- Standing by. - We got our man.
一号目标是男性白人 40岁 矮个...
Target number one is a white male, 40s, short...
身穿褐色衬衣 带灰色便帽
wearing a tan shirt and a gray tam.
收到
Copy your description.
11-34呼叫监视组 两个目标都离开了
11-34 to Surveillance, both targets are on the move.
我们无法确认车辆
We can't make the vehicle from here,
- 但是你们应该可以 - 收到
- but you sure can. - Copy.
他手里拿着那玩意儿是要干什么?
What was he doing with that thing in his hand?
和你经常用手干的活儿一样
Same thing you always do.
可能是在发短信
Probably sending a text message.
我的孩子们就爱干这个
My kids are crazy over that.
这是我们的目标 对吧?
That's our guy, right?
是街头贩毒的那个Sobotka家的家伙?
What's his face Sobotka from the drug corner?
我要见Vondas
I need to get with Vondas.
谁?
Who's that?
Spiros
Spiros.
他在哪?
Where is he?
我不认识什么Spiros
I don't know no Spiros.
- 不可能吧 - 他跳起来给了他一下?
- No shit. - He just up and clocked him?
Daniels让在场的人 把看到的都写了下来
Daniels had everybody write what they saw.
- 甚至包括穿的衣服 - 聪明 Daniels很聪明
- Even us suits. - That was smart. Daniels is sharp.
- Prez现在在哪 - Daniels送他回家了
- Where's Prez now? - Daniels took him home.
我认为他是回不了专案组了
I don't think he'll come back to this detail.
这可不一定
You never know.
他也许有什么精神异常的标签
He might have one of those psychological
贴在他的外套上...
bullshit things in his jacket...
那样他就有免罪金牌了
gives him immunity or something.
Valchek给了他免罪金牌 但是他却给了Valchek颜色看
Valchek gave him immunity, and he just put Valchek on his ass.
自从Howard堡接头之后 就没有什么动静了
Nothing since the Fort Howard meet.
他们肯定是不用电话了
They're definitely dumping phones.
Lester
Lester...
当你使用电话时
When you use a cell phone
按下"发送" 那电话会被打到哪里?
and press "send," where does the call go to?
- 为什么这么问 - 出现在Howard堡的那个老大
- Why are you asking? - The Boss Man at Fort Howard.
他把我们监听的那个手机扔了 对吧?
He tosses the cell phone we're up on, right?
然后他拿出另一个玩意儿
Then he pulls out another thingamajig,
输入了短信
and he types a message.
那就是发了条信息
Text messaging.
首先发送到周围基站中的一个 对吧?
It starts at one of those towers they got up all over the place, right?
最后传递到无线通信运营商的 一台计算机里
And ends up in a computer at a wireless provider.
如果你知道什么时候打的电话
If you knew when the call was made,
你可以返回去追踪到那个基站吗?
could you trace the call back to that tower?
如果可以的话 你也许能搞到电话号码 对吧?
'Cause if you could, mightn't you get a phone number?
搞到了号码 就可以搞到通信记录 对吧
You get that, then you got the billing details, right?
傻瓜 你知道有多少人用手机吗?
Fool, do you have any idea how many people use cell phones?
肯定有无数的人随时都在用手机
There must be thousands, hundreds of thousands at any time.
你需要的是另一个变量
What you need is another variable.
另一个数据使你能够
Another bit of data that's gonna help you
把目标电话从其他电话中分离出来
isolate your call from all the others.
如果你知道电话是从哪打出来的?
What if you knew where the call was made?
我的意思是 非常确切的地点
I mean, exactly where it was made.
我们可是在茫茫的海上
We were out in the middle of nowhere.
这样还能缩小范围吗?
Does that help narrow it down?
当然 Howard堡海堤啊
Yeah, The Fort Howard sea wall.
又不是Charles和Baltimore的马路
It ain't exactly Charles and Baltimore Streets.
还有另一个问题 哪家运营商?
You've got another problem. Which wireless company?
那里有Verizon MCI AT&T Sprint之类的一大堆...
There must be Verizon, MCI, AT&T, Sprint...
靠 又不是简单的传声筒 它们到处都是
Shit, tin cans and a string. You got dozens of them.
Lamar?
- 我的Harper's杂志呢 - 什么
- Where's my Harper's? - Say what?
新一期Harper's
Harper's. The new issue.
你没说啊 你要的是 新共和杂志和大西洋月刊啊...
You didn't say that one. You said The New Republic and Atlantic...
- 还有一本新的什么杂志 - 我告诉过你我要Harper's
- and a new something else. - I did not forget to tell you Harper's.
每周我都要重复一遍
Every week I tell you the same shit,
而你每周都左耳朵进右耳朵出
and every week you forget half of what I say.
明早你的第一件事 就是去报摊给我买本Harper's
Tomorrow, first thing, you go to the newsstand and you get Harper's.
还有国家杂志 这个你也经常忘
And The Nation, too, which you also managed to forget.
你知道在美国最危险的事是什么?
You know what the most dangerous thing in America is, right?
那就是一个黑人识文断字
A nigger with a library card.
我靠 这家伙整天就坐在那看东西
All damn day, he just sit there reading.
看那些东区的婊子还敢待在这儿
And damned if them Eastside bitches don't stay away.
这才是牛逼
That's real muscle, right there.
就是
True that.
可是等我们的好货都卖光了 该怎么办?
What are we gonna do when we start running out of good product?
这才是我们要自问的
That's what we need to ask ourselves.
哟 Bodie
Yo, Bodie,
如果Stringer想让东区的过来...
if Stringer want the Eastside up in here...
那为什么Barksdale还找人把他们赶走?
then why Barksdale got a man running them off?
死胡同
This is getting us nowhere.
Pyramid公司查不出目标的线索
We got nothing under Pyramid Inc...
其他电信公司也是一样
or any of the targets at any other cellular company.
就靠McNulty了
It's on McNulty then.
11-35 你到了吗?
11-35, you got the 20?
我就在这里
I'm on the spot right now.
请讲
Go.
10-4 北纬
10-4. Latitude first:
39度11分727秒
North, 39 degrees.11.727.
西经76度26分628秒
Longitude: West, 76 degrees.26.628.
听着 这是一个巧妙的花招
Now, this was a neat trick.
没人这么干过
No one ever did it before.
利用时间和GPS锁定手机
Identified a cell phone using time and GPS.
我们查到了今天下午4:45...
We got everything on the phone that was text messaging...
在那个坐标发信息的手机的一切资料
from those coordinates at 04:45 p.m. Today.
只有一张传票?
Just a subpoena?
用这个你们只能得到账户信息和电话号码
With this, you can get account information and a phone number.
如果是搜查令的话...
With a search warrant...
你能得到2个月的短信记录
you can get two months of text messages.
你能查到2个月的短信记录?
You got two months of text messages in this file?
可以 只要你有搜查令
I do, if you've got a warrant.
告诉你 朋友
Tell you what, friend.
我们这赶就回去 明天早上发搜查令
We're gonna go back and start typing that warrant tomorrow morning.
但是现在 我们想偷偷看一下...
But right now, we wouldn't mind taking a peek...
这男的过去24小时之内的记录
at what my man's been up to in the last 24 hours.
认为需要立即行动可无证搜查
紧急情况
Exigent circumstances.
多谢 伙计
Thanks, brother.
信息包点对点交换 内容是希腊文
我操
Fuck me.
好事多磨
Nothing's easy.
怎么了?
What's up?
他们把手机都扔了
They've dumped their phones.
我们正尽力拿到老大的短信记录
We're trying to get onto the Boss Man's text messaging.
他们用希腊文发的邮件
They sent that Greek mess over as email.
他把文字输进去 电脑就可以翻译出来
After he inputs, the computer will translate it.
好了
Got it.
立即关机
操
Shit.
嗨 Prissy
Hey, Prissy.
想你就会在这儿
Thought you'd be here.
王八蛋Ziggy
Fucking Ziggy.
他什么时候干过好事?
When didn't he do dumb shit?
还记得他伪造成人证的事吗?
Remember when he forged that Age of Majority card?
我们把钱凑在一起
We all pooled our money.
你开车把我们从Brooklyn公园带到折扣店
You drove us over Brooklyn Park to the cut-rate.
开着我妈的土黄色雪弗兰
My mom's puke-yellow Chevy.
我们特意告诉他
We told him specifically:
两瓶Pikesville Rye...(黑麦威士忌 马里兰特产)
Two bottles of Pikesville Rye
和...
and...
给我带瓶Southern Comfort(以美国波本威士忌为基酒的甜酒)
Southern Comfort for me.
那傻蛋带的是什么?
What did fucknuts get?
他妈的Boone's Farm(便宜的麦芽酒饮料)
Fucking Boone's Farm.
他说大学生就喝这种
He said that's what the college kids drank.
但是我们还是一口干了 就在这
But we did it up Right here.
嗯
Yeah.
他站在那儿
He stood up there,
一手拿一瓶...
a bottle in each hand...
喊得震天响
screaming loud enough to wake the nuns.
他喊了什么?
What the fuck did he say?
"大学生万岁!"
"College kids ain't shit!"
该死的 Zig
Goddamn, Zig.
- 嗯 - Beadie 我是Kima
- Yeah? - Beadie, it's Kima.
- Kima - 我们要去抓老大了
- Kima. - We're gonna take the Boss out.
突袭? 今晚?
Raids? Tonight?
你能把孩子安顿好吗?
You got somewhere to drop the kids off?
可以 没问题
No, no problem.
我可以把他们送到我父母那儿去
I can take them over to my parents'.
好的 到时见
All right, we'll see you soon.
Kima 多谢通知我 再见
Kima, thanks for the call. Bye.
法官想知道还要多久
The judge wants to know how much longer.
快了
We're close.
把这些扔了
Dump this row.
电脑也扔了 都扔了
Dump the computer. Dump this.